the issue of the sher the truth is that it is
el tema de las sher la verdad es que es
very sad no And then today look today
muy triste no Y entonces hoy fíjate hoy
eh both on tele5 and Antena 3 they have
eh tanto en tele5 como en Antena 3 han
shared this this clip it is a
compartido este este clip es un
super emotional piece Eh okay it is a
trocillos super emotivo Eh vale es un
super emotional piece of David bval with
trocito super emotivo de David bval con
his
su
father How are you
padre Cómo te
doing very well Hey well they
encuentras bien muy bien Oye pues me han
told me that then you were a bador
contado que entonces fuiste bador
no and one of the good ones you were a newsboy no and one
no y de los buenos fuiste voceador no y
of the good ones this same thing was told there
de los buenos esto mismo lo contó allí
on El Hormiguero eh And one of the good ones my
en El Hormiguero eh Y de los buenos mi
father mine was also a
padre el mío también fue
newsboy my father was also a newsboy I
voceador mi padre también fue voceador
think that there the man said don't tell me a
creo que ahí ha dicho el hombre no me
name Ah what name did he have What name did he have
nobre Ah que nombre tenía Qué nombre
What name did he have well my
tenía Qué nombre tenía pues mi
father's name is José
padre se llama José
carill That's me he says let's see let's see
carill Ese soy yo dice a ver vamos a
let's see
ver vamos a ver a
José shouting it's
José voceando
not
no es
this eye eh that I think it is
este ojo eh que creo que es
this one and it was with Antonio Bisbal
este y fue con Antonio Bisbal
Honestly Do you think that Rubén Olivares
Honestamente Tú crees que Rubén Olivares
had at this time the conditions to
tenía en este momento condiciones para
aspire to a crown or were you still
aspirar a una corona o todavía te
lacking still no still he was still lacking at
faltaba todavía no todavía le faltaba en
that time he was lacking Because there were very
ese tiempo le faltaba Porque eran muy
few  fights of course it looks really
pocas peleas es que claro que se ve muy
bad it looks really
mal es que se ve muy
bad let's see here there's another one wait
mal a ver aquí hay otro espera
eh Of course of course it is yes it is yes it is
eh Claro claro que es sí es sí es
Look
Mira
s José bval
s José bval
Spain yes it is yes it is he it is he it is seen It can be seen that it is him it can be
Spain sí es sí es él es él se ve Se ve
seen that it is him of course Yes that is you it is that
que es él se ve que es él claro Sí ese
you are my father
eres tú es que tú eres mi padre
I am David Don't you remember me
yo soy David Es que no te acuerdas de mí
what happens is that I have grown up look at me I already have a
que lo que pasa que he crecido ya tengo
white beard and everything What a shame
mira barba blanca y todo Qué lástima
man we want a Golden chili the white one is
tío queremos guindilla Dorada la blanca
not cool A kiss go
no Mola un beso anada guapa Pero a ver
on beautiful But let's see he only has a tesa White chili Today he only has a tesa White chili here it makes me very little pain man it makes me very little pain here man What an illness eh forgive me for the expression What a [ __ ] illness man I mean I don't know if you see how in David a helplessness
si veis como en David una una impotencia
you know he feels tenderness with his father at
sabes le entra ternura con su padre en
that moment say of course it is that you are
ese momento decir claro es que tú eres
my father and I am David Look he takes off his
mi padre y yo soy David Mira se quita la
glasses No look you are my
gafa No mira eres mi
father s it is you it is that you are my
padre s es eres tú es que tú eres mi
father I am David and the man is
padre yo soy David y se queda el hombre
like to say Ugh  is that you don't remember
como diciendo Uf es que no te acuerdas
me what happens is that I've grown up
de mí que lo que pasa es que he crecido
now I have a white beard and you
ya tengo mira barba blanca y
were all bador bador from
todo fuiste bador bador de
Granada no From
granada no De
where That is remembered eh says newsboy
dónde Eso sí se acuerda eh dice voceador
from Almería eh I mean look at you eh I mean
de Almería eh o sea fíjate tú eh o sea
you don't remember I mean you don't recognize your
no te acuerdas o sea no reconoces a tu
son and you remember that you are a newsboy from
hijo y te acuerdas que eres voceador de
Almería how is that
Almería cómo es eso
man my father had Alzheimer's and it
tío mi padre tuvo Alzheimer y
is and it was in the middle of the pandemic it was horrific it is
es y fue en plena pandemia fue horroroso
such a cruel disease it is that it is
es una enfermedad tan cruel es que es
very painful man this eh
muy doloroso tío esto eh Me conmueve
This click moves me a lot Well I know that
muchísimo este click Pues yo ya sé que
you don't remember me but I do
tú no te acuerdas de mí pero yo sí me
remember you And that is the important thing
acuerdo de ti Y eso es lo importante
eh you are very handsome Pepe I love you
eh estás muy guapo Pepe te quiero
very much
mucho
says
dice
tier and sings with him and remembers the
tier y canta con él y se acuerda de la
lyrics now eh
letra ahora eh
Look at
Mira de
lair does not touch the face
lair no toca la cara
uncle of laes and
tío de laes y
la the thing about Speech why does the thing about speech
la lo del Habla por qué lo de la habla
also have to do with it the thing about speech
tiene que ver también lo de la habla
is also my grandfather had Well yes I am seeing
es mi abuelo tuvo Bueno sí estoy viendo
that many people in the chat are
que mucha gente en el chat estáis
telling me that you have been through that your
diciéndome que habéis pasado que vuestro
parents who  your grandfather that yours
padres que vuestro abuelo que vuestro
is something very common it is in the day to
tal es algo muy común está en el día a
day or rather it is something that is
día o sea es algo que está
there it is something that is
ahí es algo que está
there it is something that is something for which
ahí es algo al lo que es algo a lo que
no solution has yet been found
todavía no se le ha encontrado solución
or anything like that there are many
ninguna ni nada por el estilo hay muchas
things that still have no solution
cosas que no tienen solución todavía
eh There are many things for which no
eh Hay muchas cosas a las que no se han
solution has yet been found
encontrado todavía solución a día de
today unfortunately unfortunately despite
hoy por desgracia por desgracia a pesar
the
de los
advances the songs
avances las canciones
[Music]
[Música]
you can
tú pue
say They forget to speak you
decir Se olvidan de hablar me habéis
put me in the chat That is
puesto en el chat Eso es
so
así
yes
sí
that disease is common because of the
esa enfermedad es habitual por el
lengthening of life Ah because now
alargamiento de la vida Ah porque ahora
life is
la vida es más
longer How curious But that that is
larga Qué curioso Pero eso eso es
official what you
oficial lo que me habéis
put to me tronio
puesto tronio
tron ​​everything is lost and speech is forgotten
tron todo se pierde y el habla se olvida
What a
Qué
shame What a shame
pena Qué pena
eh
eh
[Music]
[Música]
Give me a
Dame un
hug but it seems to me that
abrazo pero es que me da la impresión
the man is like
como que el hombre se queda así
as if he wants to remember something But you
como como que algo quiere recordar Pero
don't know why he stays like that as if to
no sabes porque se queda así como
say damn it is that my life is known it is that
diciendo [__] es que se sabe mi vida es
this is my son It is that you know what I am
que este es mi hijo Es que sabes lo que
telling you what a
digo qué
shame Well there are many people
pena Bueno pues hay mucha gente
criticizing that David has brought his
criticando que David haya sacado a su
father out in the documentary I don't know what
padre en el documental no sé qué pensáis
you guys think eh I don't know what you think the truth is I don't
ustedes eh No sé qué pensáis la verdad
know what you think and I don't
no sé qué pensáis y no sé qué pensar No
know what to think I don't know what you think and I don't know what to think because
sé qué pensáis y no sé qué pensar porque
on the one hand I don't see that he shows it in an
por una parte no veo que lo enseñe de
ugly way at all because
manera para nada fea porque es que
although the clip moves me I
aunque aunque el clip me conmueve me me
loved the click in the good sense
ha encantado el click en el buen sentido
of the expression or rather eh It's not that I
de la expresión o sea eh No es que me
love that someone is like that
encante que alguien esté así
obviously I hope not but I
evidentemente ojalá que no sino que me
love the clip because it is touching it is
encanta el clip porque es conmovedor es
endearing you know but it is very sad at the
enternecedor sabes pero es muy triste a
same time it is very sad you know
su vez es muy triste sabes
eh Let's see I understand that he did it
eh A ver entiendo que lo ha hecho como
to show it and to make it visible
para mostrarlo y para visibilizarlo
because he has done it on many
porque ya lo ha hecho en muchas
occasions I don't know in the end it is
ocasiones no sé al final es decisión de
each family's decision
cada familia
eh Let's see I don't think it's the same Maybe
eh A ver no creo que sea lo mismo A lo
you show something
mejor que tú muestres algo
eh I don't know what example to give but
eh que no sé qué ejemplo ponero pero
something super unfortunate an ugly image you
algo super desafortunado una imagen fea
know but if the man Apparently yes
sabes pero si el hombre Aparentemente si
the man Apparently Well he has an
el hombre Aparentemente Pues tiene un
appearance Well he is well he is well he is handsome he is
aspecto Pues bien está está bien está
well dressed you know He has he
guapo está bien vestido sabes Tiene
has a good appearance Well nothing is what it is
tiene una buena apariencia Pues nada es
and you know  make visible okay it's a
lo que hay y se se visibiliza vale es un
nice cl it's not an ugly cl you know
cli bonito no es un cli sabes feo
and for example Carmen Sevilla the family
e por ejemplo Carmen Sevilla la familia
decided to remove her from any means
decidió quitarla de de cualquier medio
not
no
for people very very bad I know maca I
para la gente muy muy mala Ya lo sé maca
know also they always tend to
Ya lo sé además siempre suelen
be more or less the same type of people let's
ser más o menos el mismo tipo de gente a
see I would criticize that something else is shown
ver yo criticaría que se muestre otra
imagine a relative in a
cosa imagínate un familiar en una cama
hospital bed in the Niche in the you know what I'm
de hospital en el Nicho en el sabes lo
saying in the Niche of death or something
que te digo en el Nicho de muerte o algo
like that you understand But if the man is like
así me entiendes Pero si el hombre está
that in his house in his day to day life and he's
así en su casa en su día a día y está
fine you know in the end it's the reality of
bien sabes al final es la realidad de la
life I mean always all our lives we're
vida o sea siempre toda la vida nos
going to look good Well yes I do I do I'm
vamos a estar guapos Bueno yo sí yo sí
going to be like Jesús Váquez
yo voy a estar como Jesús váquez
but in life it's the reality it's
pero en la vida es que es la realidad es
the reality
la realidad